cartoonstock.com 2019-03-18

# CartoonStock - Privacy Policy

1\. What Information Do We Collect?

2\. What Do We Use Your Information For?

3\. How Do We Protect Your Information?

4\. Do We Use Cookies?

5\. Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?

6\. Third Party Links

7\. Terms And Conditions

8\. Your Consent

9\. Changes To Our Privacy Policy

10\. Access to Data

11\. Contacting Us

**1\. What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We do not store the credit or debit card details of any of our customers.

**2\. What Do We Use Your Information For?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

  * To personalize your experience; your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website; we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service; your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send order-related emails. The email address you provide will be used to send confirmation of your order including a copy of your receipt/invoice and license agreement and your image downloads.

If you subscribe to our newsletter, the email address you provide will be used to send you information, updates on new services, features and discount and promotions. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include an instant unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email. 

**3\. How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**4\. Do We Use Cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**5\. Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**6\. Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**7\. Terms And Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.cartoonstock.com/terms.asp

**8\. Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

**9\. Changes To Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**10\. Access to Data**

You have the right to be told what personal information we hold about you on our databases. You should contact us stating your full name, your address and all services from CartoonStock to which you know you subscribe or have subscribed.

**11\. Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information or the direct contact form on our Contact page.
